Guide to the Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania Records, 1945-1984 AIS.1984.28
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Consumers Digest (Box 13, Folder 11)
- United Mine Workers Strike, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Union Leadership Academy (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Public Relations (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Hospitalization (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Walk Off Work Stoppage (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Serving Training Center (Box 13, Folder 17)
- S.C.C. District (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Special Convention, Hershey Lodge, August 7, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Joseph Rhodes Jr. for US Senate, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous Reports, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Communications Workers of America Constitution, July 1981 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- IBEW Telephone Coordinating Council By-Laws, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Sharding Suspension, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Executive Meeting Minutes (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Choice of Tours (Box 13, Folder 26-27)
- Bargaining Agreement, 1977 (Box 14)
- PACT Disb., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- R.C. Bacher Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Convention, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
- PACT, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 5-9)
- Quality of Work Life (Box 15, Folder 10-12)
- Auto Insurance (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Frank Wentzel Records (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Pension Plan, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Meeting Minutes, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- 101 Reasons to Vote Against Ronald Reagan by Terence Cannon, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Part Time and Overtime Reports (Box 15, Folder 19)
- We're Fighting for the Future! Mondale and Ferraro vs. Reagan and Bush, An AFL-CIO Review of the Issues and Candidates (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Quality of Work Life Consultation and Training Report for the Bell of Pennsylvania (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Policy Committee (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
- Public Utility Commission, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Bell Company and Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania Meeting Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Agreement between Bell Telephone Company and Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, August 7, 1977 (Box 15, Volume 1)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence and Reports (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Grievances (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Frank Wentzel Notes (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Committees (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Expense Vouchers (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Elections, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Communication Workers of America Local 13000 Convention, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Executive Elections, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Wage Increase, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- PACT Activity, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Salary Committee (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Union Organizing (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Union Reorganization (Box 16, Folder 13-17)
- PACT, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Contingency Committee, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Sky Top (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Pittsburgh Audit, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Discussions (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Contingency Committee, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Finances (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Contingency Committee Administrative-Legal Councils, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence and Reports (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Contingency Committee Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Light Guide Cable (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Fiber Optic Cable (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Technology Change Committee, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 30-31)
- Election-Constitution Committee (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Wage Scales, 1977, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 33)